# EMILIANO -—ALFONSO

#### WEB DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT ME**

Music teacher and front-end fanatic who enjoys learning new technologies, creating beautiful websites and overall making the user have a good experience. When it comes to designing, I am a perfectionist. I am a person that's easy to get along with, and am always striving to be a better dev.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Fullstack Developer at Distrocuyo S.A.** (mar 2021 - present) - Development of web apps related to electricity and assets from that field, using Next.js with Styled Components.

**Teaching Assistant at Henry** (dec. 2020 - feb. 2021, may. 2021 - present) - My role is to guide students, help them understand core concepts and reinforce the theory by providing explanations and extracurricular projects.

**E-commerce Project** (dec. 2020 - jan. 2021) - Design and development of a website dedicated to selling digital videogames. Built using React, Redux, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Passport, and Flrebase.

#### **EDUCATION**

Henry Bootcamp (oct. 2020 - feb. 2021) - Fullstack Developer. 700+ hours of intensive learning. The technologies learned there include HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Github, and the SCRUM methodology.

"Luis Gianneo" College of Music, Mar del Plata (dec. 2010 - dec. 2020) - Music Teacher

### SKILLS AND SOFTWARE

HTML	Bootstrap	React	Node.js	PostgreSQL	Adobe XD
CSS	Less & Sass	Redux	Express	Git & Github	Adobe Photoshop
JavaScript	Tailwind CSS	Next.js	Sequelize	Testing	Vue.js

## CONTACT